(Kim Tae Hee)
(كيم تاى هى)
(Im Ji Yeon)
(ايم جي يون)
(Kim Sung Oh)
(كيم سونغ أوه)
(Choi Jae Rim, Jung Woon Sun)
(تشوي جاي ريم ، جونغ وون صن)
(Lies Hidden in My Garden)
(مخبأة في حديقتي)
Stop!
قف!
Look over here.
انظر هنا.
Look over here, I said!
قلت انظر هنا!
Hey, you have to do it like that.
مهلا ، عليك أن تفعل ذلك من هذا القبيل.
Done.
منتهي.
Whoa...
قف ...
Hey, it's my school uniform. Why does it look so good on you?
مرحبًا ، إنه الزي المدرسي الخاص بي.  لماذا تبدو جيدة جدا عليك؟
- Does it? - Yeah.
- هل هذا؟  - نعم.
Your school uniform is pretty. I'll keep it clean and return it to you.
زي مدرستك جميل  سأبقيها نظيفة وأعيدها لك.
Just throw it away.
فقط ارميها بعيدا.
- Why did I run away with my school uniform? - I know, you're a runaway!
- لماذا هربت بالزي المدرسي؟  - أعلم ، أنت هارب!
I'll take a really pretty one for you. Look here.
سآخذ لك واحدة جميلة حقًا.  انظر هنا.
- Do I look like a student? - Yeah.
- هل أبدو كطالب؟  - نعم.
- A middle schooler? A high schooler? - My gosh...
- طالب متوسط؟  طالب ثانوي؟  - يا إلهي...
Hey!
يا!
You can't dye your hair here! Don't you know?
لا يمكنك صبغ شعرك هنا!  الا تعلم؟
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
أنا آسف!  أنا آسف!
Hey!
يا!
Geez...
الجيز ...
Please put in your card.
الرجاء إدخال بطاقتك.
There.
هناك.
Hey, you know that your phone sucks, right?
مرحبًا ، أنت تعلم أن هاتفك سيء ، أليس كذلك؟
What's the point of making money? Get a new one!
ما الهدف من كسب المال؟  الحصول على واحدة جديدة!
- No, I can't. My mom bought it for me. - Hey...
- لا ، لا أستطيع.  امي اشترتها لي  - يا...
By the way, why did you come all the way here?
بالمناسبة ، لماذا أتيت إلى هنا؟
Do you know someone around here?
هل تعرف احدا هنا؟
Just because. There's someone.
فقط لأن.  هناك شخص ما.
- Hey. - Huh?
- يا.  - هاه؟
You go on ahead.
تفضل.
- I'll meet with someone first. - Why?
- سألتقي بشخص ما أولاً.  - لماذا؟
Why?
لماذا؟
Hey!
يا!
Hey, Park Seung Jae!
مرحبًا ، بارك سيونغ جاي!
Nice to meet you. I'm Lee Soo Min.
سعيد بلقائك.  أنا لي سو مين.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Bus No. 734 is arriving soon.
ستصل الحافلة رقم 734 قريبًا.
We live in the same neighborhood.
نحن نعيش في نفس الحي.
How come I've never seen you before?
لماذا لم أرك من قبل؟
I know. I guess only I noticed you.
أنا أعرف.  أعتقد فقط أنني لاحظت لك.
I know your mom and dad, too.
أنا أعرف والدتك وأبيك أيضًا.
Your mom is really pretty.
والدتك جميلة حقا.
Yes.
نعم.
I guess she is.
اعتقد انها.
You don't resemble her at all. You resemble your dad.
أنت لا تشبهها على الإطلاق.  أنت تشبه والدك.
That's not true! I look exactly like my mom!
هذا ليس صحيحا!  أنا أبدو بالضبط مثل أمي!
You look very happy.
تبدو سعيدا جدا.
Are you happy?
هل أنت سعيد؟
What are you talking about?
عن ماذا تتحدث؟
You're so funny.
أنت مضحك جدا.
What's the big deal? Tell me.
ما هي الصفقة الكبيرة؟  أخبرني.
Are you happy? Are you glad you were born?
هل أنت سعيد؟  هل أنت سعيد لأنك ولدت؟
What are you saying?
ماذا تقول؟
Gosh. The midterm exam is next week.
يا الهي.  الامتحان النصفي الأسبوع المقبل.
Do you have the book, "Definition of Math," by chance?
هل لديك كتاب "تعريف الرياضيات" بالصدفة؟
Yes.
نعم.
That's great! Could you loan it to me?
ذلك رائع!  هل يمكن أن تقرضها لي؟
Okay.
تمام.
It's probably at home.
ربما يكون في المنزل.
Well...
حسنًا...
If so,
لو ذلك،
I want to come over to your house.
أريد أن آتي إلى منزلك.
What?
ماذا؟
Why? Can't I?
لماذا؟  لا أستطيع؟
I'm sorry. I dropped it by mistake.
أنا آسف.  لقد أسقطته عن طريق الخطأ.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
You'll get hurt. Go over there.
سوف تتأذى.  اذهب إلى هناك.
It's dangerous. Come down.
انه خطير.  إهدأ.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
I'll die, worst-case scenario.
سأموت ، السيناريو الأسوأ.
Why would you say that?
لماذا تريد ان تقول ذلك؟
Come down right now.
تعال الآن.
Someone told me once
قال لي أحدهم ذات مرة
that I shouldn't have been born.
لا يجب أن أكون قد ولدت.
What a terrible thing to say.
يا له من شيء فظيع أن أقوله.
Who do they think they are to say such a thing?
من يعتقدون أنهم سيقولون مثل هذا الشيء؟
Park Jae Ho.
بارك جاي هو.
Your dad.
والدك.
Right? The director of Kioomai Hospital.
يمين؟  مدير مستشفى كيوماي.
I was curious...
كنت فضوليا...
to see how someone who says stuff like that lives.
لنرى كيف يعيش شخص يقول أشياء كهذه.
What are you talking about right now?
ما الذي تتحدث عنه الآن؟
How do you know my dad?
كيف تعرف ابي؟
Park Seung Jae.
بارك سيونغ جاي.
You should've asked me how I knew your name first.
كان يجب أن تسألني كيف عرفت اسمك أولاً.
Didn't your mom tell you not to let strangers in your house?
ألم تخبرك والدتك ألا تدع الغرباء في منزلك؟
Who are you?
من أنت؟
What's this?
ما هذا؟
You know. Why do you ask?
أنت تعرف.  لماذا تسأل؟
You see this, right?
ترى هذا ، أليس كذلك؟
Two lines mean that you're pregnant.
سطرين يعني أنك حامل.
Why...
لماذا...
are you showing me this?
هل تريني هذا
Your mom.
والدتك.
She's so pretty, but...
إنها جميلة جدًا ، لكن ...
I'll end up winning, anyway.
سأنتهي بالفوز على أي حال.
I'll get going.
سأذهب.
Thanks for the juice.
شكرا على العصير.
You said something so strange.
لقد قلت شيئًا غريبًا جدًا.
I-I...
الثاني ...
I don't really understand it.
أنا لا أفهم ذلك حقًا.
Park Seung Jae.
بارك سيونغ جاي.
Listen carefully.
إستمع جيدا.
So I'm saying...
لذلك أنا أقول ...
you might have to call me "Mom."
قد تضطر إلى مناداتي ب "أمي".
Take care, then.
اعتن بنفسك ، إذن.
I'll come back when your younger sibling gets bigger.
سأعود عندما يكبر أخوك الأصغر.
(Mom: Seung Jae, I'm at Grandpa's house. There are snacks in the fridge.)
(الأم: سونغ جاي ، أنا في منزل جدي. توجد وجبات خفيفة في الثلاجة.)
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
(September 9)
(9 سبتمبر)
(September 10)
(10 سبتمبر)
You haven't left yet.
لم تغادر بعد.
No, I'm leaving now.
لا ، سأرحل الآن.
Why did you come back in?
لماذا عدت في؟
I forgot a document for the seminar.
لقد نسيت وثيقة للندوة.
I see.
أرى.
(September 18) Honey.
(18 سبتمبر) العسل.
What are you doing over there?
ماذا تفعل هناك؟
I keep noticing a foul smell these few days.
ما زلت ألاحظ رائحة كريهة هذه الأيام القليلة.
I thought maybe a stray cat buried a mouse.
اعتقدت ربما قطة ضالة دفنت فأرا.
I want to try digging it up.
أريد أن أحاول حفرها.
(September 19)
(19 سبتمبر)
Under the ground...
تحت الارض...
I'm sorry! I was kidding!
أنا آسف!  كنت امزح!
Drink it. Mom told you to drink it while it's warm.
اشربه.  أخبرتك أمي أن تشربه وهو دافئ.
Drink it.
اشربه.
Min Soo gifted it to me.
مين سو أهداه لي.
It's apparently good for anxiety relief.
يبدو أنه جيد لتخفيف القلق.
Try some.
جرب بعض.
(September 20)
(20 سبتمبر)
Seung Jae.
سيونغجاي.
Your dad and I need to talk.
أنا وأبيك بحاجة للتحدث.
Go upstairs.
اذهب للطابق العلوي.
Mom.
أم.
Go to your room.
اذهب إلى غرفتك.
The things she said to Seung Jae.
الأشياء التي قالتها لـ Seung Jae.
Do you believe what someone like her said?
هل تصدق ما قاله شخص مثلها؟
I only saw her at the hospital parking lot once. That's all.
رأيتها في موقف سيارات المستشفى مرة واحدة فقط.  هذا كل شئ.
You just saw her once.
لقد رأيتها للتو مرة واحدة.
But why would she lie to Seung Jae like that?
لكن لماذا تكذب على سونغ جاي هكذا؟
I guess the broker who finds girls like her
أعتقد أن الوسيط الذي يجد فتيات مثلها
got a few doctors at the hospital involved.
شارك فيها عدد قليل من الأطباء في المستشفى.
I was worried it'd come up during the merger,
كنت قلقة من حدوث ذلك أثناء الاندماج ،
so I confronted her about it.
لذلك واجهتها حول هذا الموضوع.
She ended up visiting me out of spite.
انتهى بها الأمر بزيارتي على الرغم من ذلك.
You know kids these days. They're so reckless.
أنت تعرف الأطفال هذه الأيام.  إنهم متهورون للغاية.
Not to mention kids like her.
ناهيك عن الأطفال مثلها.
I shouldn't have underestimated her for being a kid.
لم يكن يجب أن أقلل من شأنها لكوني طفلة.
Why didn't you tell me?
لماذا لم تخبرني
I was the only one who didn't know what happened to my son in my house.
كنت الوحيد الذي لم يعرف ماذا حدث لابني في منزلي.
Not only that, I mentioned the smell,
ليس هذا فقط ، لقد ذكرت الرائحة ،
but you ignored me.
لكنك تجاهلتني.
If I told you...
لو أخبرتك...
If I had told you, what could you have done about it?
إذا كنت قد أخبرتك ، فماذا كان يمكنك أن تفعل حيال ذلك؟
For whose sake do you think we kept it a secret?
من أجل من تعتقد أننا أبقينا الأمر سرا؟
No.
لا.
That was just an excuse
كان هذا مجرد ذريعة
to deceive me completely.
لخداعني تمامًا.
Does that matter right now?
هل هذا مهم الآن؟
Lee Soo Min.
لي سو مين.
Where is she?
أين هي؟
The night I was supposed to go night fishing with Kim Yoon Beom.
في الليلة التي كان من المفترض أن أذهب فيها للصيد مع كيم يون بيوم.
I took care of her that night.
لقد اعتنيت بها في تلك الليلة.
Just forget about it.
فقط انسى الأمر.
That's our only option right now for the sake of Seung Jae.
هذا هو خيارنا الوحيد الآن من أجل Seung Jae.
Was she an object or a plant?
هل كانت كائنًا أم نباتًا؟
She was a person.
كانت شخصا.
She was just a 15-year-old girl!
كانت مجرد فتاة تبلغ من العمر 15 عامًا!
Did I kill her?
هل قتلتها؟
Our son...
ابننا...
Seung Jae killed her.
قتلها سونغ جاي.
I'm his dad.
أنا والده.
What more could I possibly do?
ماذا يمكنني أن أفعل أكثر من ذلك؟
I'll go to the police station with Seung Jae right now.
سأذهب إلى مركز الشرطة مع سيونغ جاي الآن.
I can't just watch him being tormented.
لا يمكنني فقط مشاهدته وهو يتعرض للتعذيب.
Are you out of your mind?
هل جننت؟
Seung Jae is only 15.
سيونغ جاي يبلغ من العمر 15 عامًا فقط.
Do you want to ruin his life?
هل تريد أن تدمر حياته؟
You know what kind of person our Seung Jae is.
أنت تعرف أي نوع من الأشخاص هو Seung Jae.
He won't be able to handle the guilt throughout his life.
لن يكون قادرًا على تحمل الذنب طوال حياته.
I know how terrible that feels.
أنا أعرف كم هو فظيع هذا الشعور.
I can't let him live that way.
لا يمكنني السماح له بالعيش بهذه الطريقة.
You're worried he'd end up like you?
هل أنت قلق من أن ينتهي به الأمر مثلك؟
Seung Jae is my son.
سونغ جاي هو ابني.
He's not that weak!
إنه ليس بهذا الضعف!
If you really want to go to the police station,
إذا كنت تريد حقًا الذهاب إلى مركز الشرطة ،
go, then.
اذهب اذا.
It'd all be over then.
سينتهي كل شيء بعد ذلك.
Over?
زيادة؟
What do you mean by that?
ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
This house.
هذا البيت.
The hospital.
المستشفى.
Including Seung Jae's future.
بما في ذلك مستقبل Seung Jae.
Everything we've been working for will crumble.
كل شيء كنا نعمل من أجله سوف ينهار.
If that happens, I won't be able to handle it,
إذا حدث ذلك ، فلن أتمكن من التعامل معه ،
not just Seung Jae.
ليس فقط سونغ جاي.
So...
لذا...
So, is that why you've been hiding it all along?
إذن ، هل هذا هو السبب في أنك تخفيها طوال الوقت؟
I'm the head of this family
أنا رب هذه العائلة
and my responsibility is to protect this family.
ومسؤوليتي هي حماية هذه العائلة.
What do you think I could've done?
ماذا تعتقد أنه كان بإمكاني فعله؟
Should I have taken him to the police station for killing someone,
هل كان يجب أن آخذه إلى مركز الشرطة لقتله شخصًا ،
shut down the hospital,
أغلق المستشفى ،
and let him be ridiculed for the rest of his life?
ودعه يسخر منه ما تبقى من حياته؟
No.
لا.
No, I can't do that.
لا ، لا يمكنني فعل ذلك.
If you can't understand that,
إذا كنت لا تستطيع فهم ذلك ،
could we continue...
هل يمكننا الاستمرار ...
to be a family?
لتكون عائلة؟
(Hwaju Police Station)
(مركز شرطة حواجو)
(Adult diapers. Buy one, get one free event.) Hello?
(حفاضات للكبار. اشتر واحدة واحصل على مناسبة مجانية). مرحبًا؟
I'll be there by 11.
سأكون هناك بحلول سن 11.
Those are the event items!
تلك هي عناصر الحدث!
The elders don't like the complimentary ones because they're scratchy and uncomfortable.
كبار السن لا يحبون المجاملة لأنهم مشوشون وغير مرتاحين.
So everyone gets those instead.
لذلك يحصل الجميع على هؤلاء بدلاً من ذلك.
You should stock up since the event doesn't happen often!
يجب أن تخزن لأن الحدث لا يحدث كثيرًا!
(Lies Hidden in My Garden)
(مخبأة في حديقتي)
Did you know that woman was coming, too?
هل تعلم أن تلك المرأة كانت قادمة أيضًا؟
(Hwaju Police Station)
(مركز شرطة حواجو)
The place Lee Soo Min was buried
المكان الذي دُفن فيه Lee Soo Min
and the place Kim Yoon Beom was found.
والمكان الذي تم العثور فيه على Kim Yoon Beom.
They happened to be in the same place.
تصادف أن يكونوا في نفس المكان.
Kim Yoon Beom introduced me to that place
قدمني كيم يون بوم إلى ذلك المكان
since it's secluded and has clean water.
لأنه منعزل وبه مياه نظيفة.
Of all days, he had to die the day I buried Lee Soo Min.
في كل الأيام ، كان عليه أن يموت في اليوم الذي دفنت فيه لي سو مين.
No.
لا.
He might end up being the key suspect.
قد ينتهي به الأمر ليكون المشتبه به الرئيسي.
Let me ask you one thing.
دعني أسألك شيئًا واحدًا.
How did he end up with Lee Soo Min's phone?
كيف انتهى به الأمر مع هاتف Lee Soo Min؟
I guess she left it in the car when she got drunk
أعتقد أنها تركته في السيارة عندما سُكرت
and he found it while he was driving my car.
ووجدها بينما كان يقود سيارتي.
He had a tendency to steal.
كان لديه ميل للسرقة.
What if...
ماذا إذا...
Choo Sang Eun tells the police about it?
تشو سانغ يون يخبر الشرطة عن ذلك؟
She knows better than anyone that there's no evidence.
إنها تعرف أفضل من أي شخص أنه لا يوجد دليل.
And even if she digs further,
وحتى لو بحثت أكثر ،
she's the one who'd be in danger.
هي التي ستكون في خطر.
Kim Yoon Beom...
كيم يون بوم ...
was probably killed by her.
ربما قُتلت بواسطتها.
I'll call a taxi.
سأتصل بسيارة أجرة.
You can take the car.
يمكنك أن تأخذ السيارة.
I'll protect our family, no matter what.
سأحمي عائلتنا مهما حدث.
Good luck with the interview.
حظا سعيدا للمقابلة.
(Hwaju Police Station)
(مركز شرطة حواجو)
Ahjussi, can't you drive better than that?
Ahjussi ، ألا يمكنك القيادة أفضل من ذلك؟
Help me get up. Please?
ساعدني على النهوض.  لو سمحت؟
What's the deal?
ما هي الصفقة؟
People like you should've never been born.
الناس مثلك لم يكن يجب أن يولدوا أبدًا.
Green plum tea is apparently good for pregnant women.
شاي البرقوق الأخضر مفيد على ما يبدو للنساء الحوامل.
So both of you suspected your husbands' relationship with Soo Min
لذا يشتبه كلاكما في علاقة زوجك مع سو مين
and looked for her to confirm it?
وبحثت عنها لتأكيد ذلك؟
Yes.
نعم.
All of it was a misunderstanding on my part.
كل ذلك كان سوء فهم من جانبي.
Nothing happened between my husband and Soo Min.
لم يحدث شيء بين زوجي وسو مين.
Grasshopper. You know him, right?
الجراد.  أنت تعرفه ، أليس كذلك؟
His real name is Joo Tae Gyung.
اسمه الحقيقي هو جو تاي جيونج.
Yes.
نعم.
He said he got this phone from some ladies.
قال إنه حصل على هذا الهاتف من بعض السيدات.
It was you two, right?
كنتما الاثنان ، أليس كذلك؟
Yes.
نعم.
Who was in possession of
الذي كان في حوزة
Lee Soo Min's phone originally?
هاتف Lee Soo Min في الأصل؟
Ms. Choo Sang Eun.
السيدة تشو سانغ اون.
It's true.
انها حقيقة.
I had it.
كان لي.
Since my husband had it.
منذ أن حصل عليها زوجي.
How strange.
كم هذا غريب.
You're certain he was killed, but...
أنت متأكد من أنه قُتل ، لكن ...
why didn't you turn this into the police?
لماذا لم تحول هذا إلى الشرطة؟
It could've helped with the investigation.
كان من الممكن أن يساعد في التحقيق.
- Ms. Choo Sang Eun. - You must know if you saw it.
- السيدة تشو سانغ اون.  - يجب أن تعرف إذا رأيت ذلك.
I didn't even know what kind of stuff he did with her.
لم أكن أعرف حتى نوع الأشياء التي كان يفعلها معها.
It's not like I'd want everyone to know about it.
ليس الأمر كما لو أنني أريد أن يعرف الجميع عنها.
(Lee Soo Min, Age: 15)
(لي سو مين ، العمر: 15)
Well, Ms. Moon.
حسنًا ، السيدة مون.
Oh!
أوه!
Oh! You are in shock!
أوه!  أنت في حالة صدمة!
I'm sorry! I was going to put them away!
أنا آسف!  كنت سأضعهم بعيدا!
By chance...
مصادفة...
do you think it's possible that Mr. Kim
هل تعتقد أنه من الممكن أن يكون السيد كيم
killed Soo Min and decided to kill himself
قتل سو مين وقرر قتل نفسه
out of guilt at all?
بدافع الذنب على الإطلاق؟
Ms. Choo Sang Eun.
السيدة تشو سانغ اون.
I'm not sure, either.
لست متأكدًا أيضًا.
We're done!
لقد انتهينا!
You can leave now.
يمكنك المغادرة الآن.
Thank you!
شكرًا لك!
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
was Soo Min reported missing?
هل تم الإبلاغ عن فقدان سو مين؟
How did you know?
كيف عرفت؟
The day before the body was found,
قبل يوم من العثور على الجثة ،
her father reported her missing.
أبلغ والدها عن فقدها.
You could say he was lucky.
يمكنك القول أنه كان محظوظا.
Okay, then. Have a good day.
حسنا إذا.  اتمنى لك يوم جيد.
Unfortunately, your husband's case will be concluded
للأسف ستنتهي قضية زوجك
as suicide, as I told you before.
على أنه انتحار ، كما أخبرتك من قبل.
He was suddenly dismissed from work, got sued multiple times,
تم فصله فجأة من العمل وتمت مقاضاته عدة مرات ،
and he was pressured financially, too.
وتعرض لضغوط مالية أيضًا.
You said you didn't know, right?
قلت إنك لا تعرف ، أليس كذلك؟
No, not at all.
لا إطلاقا.
It must've been tough for you. Thank you for coming all the way here.
يجب أن يكون الأمر صعبًا بالنسبة لك.  شكرا لك على القدوم إلى هنا.
Do you want to pick up Mr. Kim's belongings?
هل تريد اصطحاب متعلقات السيد كيم؟
It's quite a distance to come here from Seoul.
إنها مسافة بعيدة جدًا عن المجيء إلى هنا من سيول.
I'll take them.
سآخذهم.
I guess it's really all over now.
أعتقد أن الأمر انتهى حقًا الآن.
So as our misunderstandings.
حتى سوء الفهم لدينا.
Misunderstandings?
سوء تفاهم؟
Lee Soo Min's phone.
هاتف لي سو مين.
Dr. Park Jae Ho had it originally.
كان لدى الدكتور بارك جاي هو ذلك في الأصل.
My husband just stole it from him.
زوجي سرقها منه للتو.
Did you...
هل فعلت...
say that to the police, too?
أقول ذلك للشرطة أيضا؟
No.
لا.
Not yet.
ليس بعد.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
(Kim Yoon Beom. May he rests in peace.)
(كيم يون بوم. أتمنى أن يستريح بسلام).
We don't usually call the family unless it's serious.
نحن عادة لا نتصل بالعائلة إلا إذا كان الأمر جادًا.
But Ms. Yoon Myung Soon...
لكن السيدة يون ميونغ قريبا ...
You must know since she's your mother,
يجب أن تعرف بما أنها والدتك ،
but she's really something.
لكنها حقًا شيء ما.
She's extremely difficult than most.
إنها صعبة للغاية أكثر من غيرها.
Give it to me. I'll do it.
اعطني اياه.  سأفعل ذلك.
Oh! I almost forgot.
أوه!  انا تقريبا نسيت.
Someone at the administration was looking for you.
كان شخص ما في الإدارة يبحث عنك.
They haven't been paid for the outpatient treatments and medicines.
لم يتم الدفع لهم مقابل علاجات العيادات الخارجية والأدوية.
They wanted me to tell you that.
أرادوا مني أن أخبرك بذلك.
I'm not saying everyone does it,
أنا لا أقول أن الجميع يفعل ذلك ،
but people sometimes disappear, leaving their family members here.
لكن الناس يختفون في بعض الأحيان ، تاركين أفراد عائلاتهم هنا.
Oh, the laundry room is on the second floor.
أوه ، غرفة الغسيل في الطابق الثاني.
- Hello? - Ms. Choo! I did it! I did it!
- مرحبًا؟  - السيدة تشو!  أنا فعلت هذا!  أنا فعلت هذا!
The apartment was rented!
تم تأجير الشقة!
The new tenant signed the lease today.
وقع المستأجر الجديد عقد الإيجار اليوم.
You have to move out by October 10th, okay?
يجب أن تغادر بحلول العاشر من أكتوبر ، حسنًا؟
The 10th?
العاشر؟
How could I move out so quickly?
كيف يمكنني الخروج بهذه السرعة؟
Why? Do you want me to find a place for you?
لماذا؟  هل تريدني أن أجد لك مكانًا؟
Okay, then.
حسنا إذا.
It's that pretty lady!
إنها تلك السيدة الجميلة!
(Park Jae Ho)
(بارك جاي هو)
(Kioomai Children's General Hospital, Director Park Jae Ho)
(مستشفى كيوماي العام للأطفال ، مدير بارك جاي هو)
(MOU Signing Ceremony For Building a Children's General Hospital)
(حفل توقيع مذكرة التفاهم لبناء مستشفى عام للأطفال)
Congratulations.
تهانينا.
Wow! I thought it'd be impossible. Can't believe this day came, Sunbae!
رائع!  اعتقدت أنه سيكون من المستحيل.  لا أصدق أن هذا اليوم جاء ، سنباي!
You'd better get it together, too.
من الأفضل أن تجمعها معًا أيضًا.
Don't try to do anything funny again.
لا تحاول أن تفعل أي شيء مضحك مرة أخرى.
I know!
أنا أعرف!
I'm regretting it a lot, Dr. Park Jae Ho!
أنا نادم على ذلك كثيرًا ، دكتور بارك جاي هو!
Shouldn't we celebrate this evening?
ألا يجب أن نحتفل هذا المساء؟
We should call Min Soo hyung, too.
يجب أن ندعو مين سو هيونغ أيضًا.
Min Soo hyung! Speak of the devil!
مين سو هيونغ!  الحديث عن الشيطان!
What? Yeah.
ماذا؟  نعم.
You received a call?
هل تلقيت مكالمة؟
Yes.
نعم.
All right.
حسنًا.
Why? What is it?
لماذا؟  ما هذا؟
He got a call from the police station asking if he knew Lee Soo Min.
تلقى مكالمة من مركز الشرطة يسأل عما إذا كان يعرف لي سو مين.
I think it's the police. Shit!
أعتقد أنها الشرطة.  القرف!
Sunbae, what should Min Soo hyung and I do?
سنباي ، ماذا يجب أن أفعل أنا ومين سو هيونغ؟
Sunbae...
سنباي ...
Gun Hoo.
غون هوو.
Why are you asking me that?
لماذا تسألني ذلك؟
I have nothing to do with it.
لا علاقة لي به.
So, if it's concluded as suicide, the insurance money...
لذا ، إذا انتهى الأمر على أنه انتحار ، فإن أموال التأمين ...
You don't get a single penny?
لا تحصل على فلس واحد؟
- Apparently. - My gosh!
- فيما يبدو.  - يا إلهي!
What will you do from now on?
ماذا ستفعل من الآن فصاعدا؟
The baby will be here in no time, too.
سيكون الطفل هنا في أي وقت من الأوقات أيضًا.
Unni.
أوني.
Can I stay over at your place in Hwaju
هل يمكنني البقاء في مكانك في Hwaju
for two or three months?
لمدة شهرين أو ثلاثة؟
Pardon?
عفو؟
The owner wants me to move out right away.
المالك يريد مني أن أخرج على الفور.
- I won't be there too long- - Well...
- لن أبقى هناك طويلا - - حسنا ...
the thing is, Sang Eun...
الشيء هو ، سانغ اون ...
Actually, next month...
في الواقع ، الشهر المقبل ...
my youngest sibling got a job around there, so
حصل شقيقي الأصغر على وظيفة هناك ، لذا
he'd be staying with us for a while. I already talked to Oppa about it.
سيبقى معنا لفترة من الوقت.  لقد تحدثت بالفعل مع أوبا حول هذا الموضوع.
And Oppa isn't as healthy as usual since he worked too much.
وأوبا ليس بصحة جيدة كالمعتاد لأنه عمل كثيرًا.
I don't think he could travel long distances anymore.
لا أعتقد أنه يستطيع السفر لمسافات طويلة بعد الآن.
We're thinking of selling the truck and opening a small kimbap shop.
نفكر في بيع الشاحنة وفتح متجر kimbap صغير.
Wouldn't you feel uncomfortable living with Oppa?
ألا تشعر بعدم الارتياح للعيش مع أوبا؟
I'll figure it out.
سأجد الحل.
I'm sorry, Sang Eun.
أنا آسف يا سانغ أون.
I'll take care of Mother. You should rest at home.
سأعتني بأمي.  يجب أن ترتاح في المنزل.
By the way, what's that? Is it yours?
بالمناسبة ، ما هذا؟  أهو لك؟
(Kim Yoon Beom. May he rests in peace.)
(كيم يون بوم. أتمنى أن يستريح بسلام).
They're his belongings.
إنها متعلقاته.
Oh! I see...
أوه!  أرى...
(Kim Yoon Beom. May he rests in peace.)
(كيم يون بوم. أتمنى أن يستريح بسلام).
(Max Townhouses. Enjoy the country lifestyle for 500 million...)
(ماكس تاون هاوس. استمتع بأسلوب حياة الريف مقابل 500 مليون ...)
Seung Jae!
سيونغ جاي!
The call is not going through. After the beep...
المكالمة لا تجري.  بعد الصافرة ...
(My Son)
(ابني)
(Seung Jae's dad)
(والد سونغ جاي)
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Well...
حسنًا...
The thing is...
الشيء هو...
Later. Let's talk later.
لاحقاً.  لنتحدث لاحقا.
I'm kind of busy right now.
أنا مشغول نوعًا ما الآن.
Seung Jae...
سيونغ جاي ...
It's about Seung Jae.
إنه يتعلق بـ Seung Jae.
I drove him here.
قدته إلى هنا.
That's all I know.
هذا كل ما اعرفه.
I'll wait here. Go see him right now.
سأنتظر هنا.  اذهب لرؤيته الآن.
Seung Jae.
سيونغجاي.
Come in first, Mom.
تعالي أولاً يا أمي.
What's this place?
ما هذا المكان؟
It'll be your home from now on.
سيكون منزلك من الآن فصاعدًا.
It looks bad now, but if you decorate it-
يبدو سيئًا الآن ، لكن إذا قمت بتزيينه-
Park Seung Jae!
بارك سيونغ جاي!
I won't go back, Mom.
لن أعود يا أمي.
Seung Jae.
سيونغجاي.
I know you're struggling right now.
أعلم أنك تكافح الآن.
- I do, but this is- - Mom.
- أنا أفعل ، لكن هذا- - أمي.
I saw everything.
رأيت كل شيء.
What did you see?
ماذا رأيت؟
Dad...
أب...
killing Lee Soo Min.
قتل لي سو مين.
I saw everything.
رأيت كل شيء.
Seung Jae, Dad left for the seminar early this morning
سونغ جاي ، غادر أبي للندوة في وقت مبكر من هذا الصباح
and I'm visiting my sick great-aunt. So I can't drive you to school.
وأنا أزور عمتي المريضة.  لذا لا يمكنني اصطحابك إلى المدرسة.
Get ready right after breakfast and leave early, okay?
استعد مباشرة بعد الإفطار وغادر مبكرًا ، حسنًا؟
Okay.
تمام.
Seung Jae, are you ready to go?
سونغ جاي ، هل أنت مستعد للذهاب؟
I'm sorry...
أنا آسف...
I'll be right back. Just wait for a moment.
سأعود حالا.  فقط انتظر لحظة.
I...
أنا...
I'll be right back.
سأعود حالا.
In the first sentence, there's a long subject.
في الجملة الأولى ، هناك موضوع طويل.
What would be the verb?
ماذا سيكون الفعل؟
The verb is...
الفعل هو ...
Seung Jae!
سيونغ جاي!
You haven't left yet.
لم تغادر بعد.
No, I'm leaving now.
لا ، سأرحل الآن.
Why did you come back in?
لماذا عدت في؟
I forgot a document for the seminar.
لقد نسيت وثيقة للندوة.
I see...
أرى...
Didn't you hear a noise from the ceiling just now?
ألم تسمع ضوضاء من السقف الآن؟
What noise?
ما الضوضاء؟
Did you take your med?
هل أخذت دواءك؟
I did.
فعلتُ.
You go ahead. I'll pick up the document and leave.
تفضل.  سألتقط المستند وأغادر.
(Pass) If you don't feel good after seeing a doctor, go home right after.
(تمرير) إذا لم تشعر بالرضا بعد رؤية الطبيب ، فارجع إلى المنزل بعد ذلك مباشرة.
Or should I come with you since it's lunch break soon?
أم يجب أن آتي معك لأن استراحة الغداء قريبًا؟
No.
لا.
Seung Jae!
سيونغ جاي!
I heard it.
سمعته.
I heard the noises she made.
سمعت الأصوات التي أحدثتها.
I definitely heard it!
لقد سمعت ذلك بالتأكيد!
I could've saved her!
كان بإمكاني أن أنقذها!
This is all my fault.
هذا هو كل خطأي.
Seung Jae, I...
سونغ جاي ، أنا ...
I couldn't trust myself.
لم أستطع الوثوق بنفسي.
That's why...
لهذا السبب...
Mom!
أم!
It's not your fault.
انها ليست غلطتك.
Dad did it.
فعلها أبي.
What's certain is that...
ما هو مؤكد هو أن ...
the one who did that to Lee Soo Min
الشخص الذي فعل ذلك مع Lee Soo Min
was dad.
كان أبي.
(Security screen locked)
(شاشة الأمان مقفلة)
(Enter Passcode)
(أدخل رمز المرور)
Moon Joo Ran.
مون جو ران.
Crazy bastard...
نذل مجنون...
(Album)
(ألبوم)
(The pink phone)
(الهاتف الوردي)
(12 Cornelia, 12th Street, Eumgang-ro, Bunnam-gu, Sungwon-shi, Gyeonggi-do)
(12 Cornelia، 12th Street، Eumgang-ro، Bunnam-gu، Sungwon-shi، Gyeonggi-do)
(Jo Gun Hoo? Park Jae Ho?)
(جو جون هو؟ بارك جاي هو؟)
(Did she meet Park Jae Ho for prostitution? And did they start dating?)
(هل قابلت بارك جاي هو من أجل الدعارة؟ وهل بدأوا في المواعدة؟)
(Is it really prostitution?)
(هل هي حقا دعارة؟)
(The pink phone's last location was Cornelia?)
(آخر موقع للهاتف الوردي كان كورنيليا؟)
(Park Jae Ho's house? Prostitution? 500 million won!)
(منزل بارك جاي هو؟ الدعارة؟ 500 مليون وون!)
(To Dr. Park Jae Ho, I correct the amount. It'll be 500 million won. See you at Banyeo Reservoir at 11 tonight.)
(إلى الدكتور بارك جاي هو ، أصحح المبلغ. سيكون 500 مليون وون. نراكم في Banyeo Reservoir في الساعة 11 الليلة.)
Is this why it was 500 million?
هل لهذا السبب كان 500 مليون؟
Moon Joo Ran, Park Jae Ho...
مون جو ران بارك جاي هو ...
(12 Cornelia)
(12 كورنيليا)
(Lies Hidden in My Garden)
(مخبأة في حديقتي)
Do you realize what you're doing right now, Ms. Moon?
هل تدرك ما تفعله الآن ، السيدة مون؟
Instigating murder.
التحريض على القتل.
Help me.
ساعدني.
How about a plan?
ماذا عن خطة؟
Do you have one?
هل لديك واحدة؟
As long as you help me, Sang Eun.
طالما كنت تساعدني ، سانغ اون.
♫ Seeing me leaving ♫
♫ رؤيتي مغادرًا ♫
♫ Your eyes... ♫
♫ عيناك ... ♫